Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Born-Digital Photographs, 1999-2019
  - Events, 1994 November 3-2016 July 14; 6; 22929 Digital Files
    - Events, 1994 November 3-2016 July 14; 6.1; 22929 Digital Files
      - Advancement: 2/17/06 @ 9:15 AM Cancer Research Center various lab shots, 2006 March 3; 358.8 MB 179 Digital Files
      - Alumni Affairs: 3/2/06 @ 9 AM Alumni House UAlbany apparel, 2006 March 14; 129.9 MB 22 Digital Files
      - President: 3/6/06 @ 9 AM location TBA Board of Visitors, 2006 March 16; 112.1 MB 56 Digital Files
      - President: 3/6/06 @ Noon location TBA Board of Visitors Luncheon, 2006 March 16; 40.4 MB 15 Digital Files
      - President: 3/7/06 @ 10:45 AM Capital Bldg. Albany SUNY Day, 2006 March 16; 82.9 MB 40 Digital Files
      - President: 3/10/06 Time and location TBA New Jobs NY w/ Hilary Clinton, 2006 March 16; 224.8 MB 105 Digital Files
      - President: 3/12/06 @ time TBA CC President's Leadership Awards Ceremony, 2006 March 16; 394.1 MB 101 Digital Files
      - President: 3/13/06 @ Noon - 1:30 PM CC (Ballroom or Assembly Hall) Minority Scholars Lunch for Albany High, 2006 March 16; 61.9 MB 30 Digital Files
      - President: 3/20/06 @ 2:30 PM Life Science Bldg Presentations for Board of Visitors, 2006 March 16; 48.9 MB 26 Digital Files
      - President: 3/20/06 @ 5:45 PM Milne 200 Board of Visitors (full group) Dinner, 2006 March 16; 128.8 MB 63 Digital Files
      - President: 3/22/06 @ 1:30 PM Standish Room Joe Persico Press Conference, 2006 March 16; 97.1 MB 50 Digital Files
      - President: 3/23/06 @ 8 AM - 5 PM location TBA Tracy Kidder / Albany Reading Project, 2006 March 16; 77.1 MB 39 Digital Files
      - President: 3/9/06 @ 3 PM - 4 PM Standish Room Linda Greenhouse class, 2006 March 16; 21.5 MB 10 Digital Files
      - President: 3/23/06 @ 5:30 PM - 8:30 PM Albany Court of Appeals President Hall lecturing / Judge Judith Kaye, 2006 March 16; 306.9 MB 105 Digital Files
      - University Development: 3/3/06 @ 9:30 AM PAC visiting Albany HS students on tour of campus, 2006 March 17; 79.1 MB 40 Digital Files
      - Jewish Studies: 5/3/06 afternoon and evening Hastings-on-Hudson Jewish Studies Celebration Dinner, 2006 March 22; 483.4 MB 203 Digital Files
      - Library: 5/2/06 @ 2 PM - 4 PM Standish Room Bread and Roses Celebration, 2006 April 3; 187.4 MB 89 Digital Files
      - Advancement: 3/22/06 @ 6:30 PM Pres Res Joe Persico Reception, 2006 April 5; 153.6 MB 70 Digital Files
      - President: 3/22/06 @ 11:45 PM Science Library President for a Day_Vincent Porfirio:, 2006 April 5; 14.8 MB 7 Digital Files
      - Advancement: 3/22/06 @ Noon Science Library / Special Archives Conference Room Joe Persico Luncheon, 2006 April 5; 53.3 MB 27 Digital Files
      - President: 3/21/06 @ 6:15 PM Albany H S press conference:, 2006 April 5; 125.7 MB 62 Digital Files
      - Library: 3/24/06 @ 10:30 AM CC Ballroom Africa and the Diaspora: Agents for Change, 2006 April 6; 93.9 MB 44 Digital Files
      - Advancement: 3/29/06 @ 9:30 AM East Campus / Cancer Ctr - Executive Board Rm 3rd Fl check presentation: First Niagara Bank Foundation, 2006 April 6; 81.6 MB 40 Digital Files
      - Sports Information: 5/1/06 @ 5 PM RACC Great Dane Awards, 2006 April 12; 637.0 MB 137 Digital Files
      - Research: 5/30/06 @ 12:15 Life Science Conferece Rm 1143 / 3 PM Life Science / Auditorium Research Colloquium, 2006 April 12; 338.4 MB 77 Digital Files
      - Arts and Sciences: 4/21/06 @ 3:30 PM SS 369 group photo: students, faculty members and Chair, 2006 May 4; 27.0 MB 10 Digital Files
      - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; 1.2 GB 597 Digital Files
      - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; 1.2 GB 597 Digital Files
      - President: 4/26/06 @ 8:30 AM President's Office President for a Day: Elizabeth Gray, 2006 May 10; 64.3 MB 31 Digital Files
      - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; 1.2 GB 597 Digital Files
      - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; 1.2 GB 597 Digital Files
      - Information Technology Services: 5/23/06 @ 9 - 10:30 AM Management Services Bldg staff meeting and group shot, 2006 May 18; 255.8 MB 59 Digital Files
      - Information Technology Services: 5/23/06 @ 9 - 10:30 AM Management Services Bldg staff meeting and group shot, 2006 May 18; 255.8 MB 59 Digital Files
      - President: 5/10/06 @ 6 PM Pres Res Valedictorian Dinner, 2006 May 24; 143.3 MB 48 Digital Files
      - Development Events: 6/3/06 @ 3:45 PM Pres Res President's Club Reception, 2006 June 13; 205.3 MB 96 Digital Files
      - Student Success: 6/12/06 @ Noon - 2 PM Science Library / West Seminar Room Albany High School Student Award Luncheon, 2006 June 14; 112.9 MB 60 Digital Files
      - Advancement: 6/8/06 @ 4 PM location TBA University Council Meeting, 2006 June 15; 137.3 MB 69 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 6/15/06 @ 8 PM Location TBA Special Olympics / Opening Ceremony, 2006 June 16; 616.9 MB 197 Digital Files
      - President: 6/6/06 - 6/7/06 Long Island, NY various locations Roads Scholar Tour / Long Island, 2006 June 22; 2.5 GB 471 Digital Files
      - Advancement: 6/13/06 @ 5:30 PM Nano Fab steps group: Jiangsu (China) visitors, 2006 June 26; 39.8 MB 26 Digital Files
      - President: 6/14/06 @ 11:30 AM Standish Room Laval Delegation, 2006 June 27; 57.9 MB 31 Digital Files
      - Advancement Events`: 6/2/06 @ 8 AM Ft. Orange Club / Albany, NY CEO Breakfast, 2006 July 3; 131.8 MB 52 Digital Files
      - Advancement: s: 7/7/06 Campus Center / Parent's Fountain portraits: Tom Bessette and Cathy Hornberger Fall 2006 UAlbany Magazine, 2006 July 20; 193.3 MB 83 Digital Files
      - Development Events: 8/14/06 @ 5 PM - 7:30 PM Standish Room / Giant's Practice NY Giant's Donor Reception, 2006 July 24; 43.6 MB 47 Digital Files
      - ETAP: 7/25/06 @ 11 AM SUNY Tunes kids doing a recording, 2006 August 8; 341.5 MB 164 Digital Files
      - Sports Information: 7/26/06 @ 11:30 AM Giant's Dutch Quad Lawn Giant's Media Day, 2006 August 9; 157.1 MB 124 Digital Files
      - Development Events: 9/21/06 @ 5:30 PM Hall of Springs, Saratoga, NY 2006 Citizen Laureate, 2006 August 10; 438.8 MB 229 Digital Files
      - Development Events: 9/21/06 @ 5:30 PM Hall of Springs, Saratoga, NY 2006 Citizen Laureate, 2006 August 10; 438.8 MB 229 Digital Files
      - Business: 9/5/06 @ 12 Noon Parent's Fountain Connections Cover Shot, 2006 August 14; 314.8 MB 65 Digital Files
      - Advancement: 9/18/06 @ 10 AM RACC Kermit Hall Tribute, 2006 October 2; 519.1 MB 229 Digital Files
      - President: Photo Session: 8/14/06 CC Small Fountain President Kermit Hall Memorial, 2006 October 2; 244.5 MB 173 Digital Files
      - President's Office: 10/3/06 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom for Fall Faculty meeting., 2006 October 3; 151.2 MB 82 Digital Files
      - Development: 10/6/06 @ 2:30 pm University Hall 208C (Check presentation of Mr. Jack Davis from Dell to Chris Haile and Deb Read), 2006 October 6; 36.5 MB 19 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 10/16/06 @ 10:30 AM University Hall Atrium; 10:45 AM Brief Program; 11 AM of People touring the building and any outside shot if needed all for University Hall Open House., 2006 October 16; 110.7 MB 57 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 10/18/06 @ 8:30 am at Albany High School for Albany High School Teach Out, 2006 October 18; 20.9 MB 35 Digital Files
      - Center for Autism: 10/18/06 @ 11 AM Desmond Hotel for Autism conference., 2006 October 18; 36.0 MB 18 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 10/20/06 @ 12-1:30 pm CC Ballroom for Alumni Awareness Kick off event, 2006 October 19; 203.9 MB 95 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 10/20/06 @ 12-1:30 pm CC Ballroom for Alumni Awareness Kick off event, 2006 October 19; 203.9 MB 95 Digital Files
      - Development: 10/20/06 @ 2-3:30 Page Hall for Mental Health Forum for SSW 40th Anniversary., 2006 October 20; 71.3 MB 33 Digital Files
      - Development: 10/20/06 @ 4:45 - 5:45 Milne 200 for SSW 40th Anniversary event, 2006 October 20; 149.5 MB 73 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/5/06 @ 2 PM UAB Emeritus Center / Ray Ortali, Bill Reese and Toby Clyman, 2006 October 20; 52.7 MB 30 Digital Files
      - Development: 10/21/06 @ 9:30 - 11 am Standish Room for Alumni Weekend event - Presidents Club Champagne Brunch, 2006 October 21; 23.7 MB 72 Digital Files
      - Development: 10/25/06 @ 4-8:30 pm NYC for Foundation Board meeting and reception., 2006 October 25; 212.8 MB 120 Digital Files
      - Development: 10/25/06 @ 4-8:30 pm NYC for Foundation Board meeting and reception., 2006 October 25; 21.4 MB 61 Digital Files
      - Governmental Public and Media Relations: 10/18/06 @ 10 AM University Hall Atrium for McNulty Press Event / NERFI Dept of Justice Grant, 2006 October 26; 134.8 MB 69 Digital Files
      - NYLARNET: 11/3/06 @ 9:45 - 10:30 AM Campus Center Assembly Hall for Latino Immigration Policy Conference, 2006 November 3; 102.8 MB 53 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 11/1/06 @ 4 PM Emeritus Center (UAB?) for Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2006 November 4; 66.7 MB 38 Digital Files
      - Development: 11/9/06 from 5:30 - 7:30, Art Museum for Donor Recognition Reception., 2006 November 9; 165.5 MB 83 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 11/14/06 @ 1 - 2 PM Patroon Room for photo of Professor Angie Chung and Food for Thought program, 2006 November 14; 32.5 MB 15 Digital Files
      - Development: 11/15/06 from 5:30 - 7:30 pm, Liife Sciences building for Life Sciences Donor Recognition event., 2006 November 15; 24.1 MB 58 Digital Files
      - President's Office: photo shoot: 11/13/06 @ 4:30 PM in Sub-Basement Studio for Holiday Card, 2006 November 15; 150.6 MB 179 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 11/29/06 @ 3 p.m. Art Museum for photo of a dress rehearsal of a performance marking the 35th anniversary of the Women's Studies department at UAlbany, 2006 November 30; 36.9 MB 25 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 12/11/06 @ 10:30 am UNH Atrium for photo of Whitney Sperrazza addressing the prospective student tour., 2006 December 12; 77.7 MB 39 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 12/12/06 @ 8 pm Recording Studios of the Lecture Center Sub-basement for photo of Whitney Sperrazza rehearsing with Serendipity., 2006 December 13; 77.2 MB 42 Digital Files
      - President's Office: 12/13/06 @ 12 Noon Standish Room for photo of Valedictorian Luncheon 12/13/06 @ 2:30 p.m. UNH Atrium for Faculty/staff holiday party, 2006 December 14; 25.4 MB 62 Digital Files
      - Small Business Development: 01/03/07 @ 10 a.m. Goold Orchards 1297 Brookview Station Road, Castleton, NY for photo of company., 2007 January 4; 232.4 MB 105 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 01/11/07 at 2 p.m. UAB 437 for PDP Open House., 2007 January 11; 80.7 MB 40 Digital Files
      - Center for Autism: 2/1 /07 @ 4:00 pm 1535 Western Ave for Center for Autism ribbon cutting. Types of shots needed: pictures of the ribbon cutting, during the reception, of the building out from with our sign, and a picture of the staff with the Dean and Provost. Need photos in both and hi and low res, 2007 February 2; 38.4 MB 106 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 2/2/07 @ 12 - 1:30 PM SEFCU Arena for photo Lee McElroy Contract Signing, 2007 February 2; 39.5 MB 90 Digital Files
      - Chancellor's Office: 3/1/07 @ 11 AM - 1:30 PM Fireside Lounge, Campus Center for Chancellor's Listening Tour, 2007 March 1; 27.5 MB 80 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 4/27/07 @ 10:30 AM UNH Atrium for Design Entry Media Event, 2007 March 6; 45.2 MB 47 Digital Files
      - Provost's Office: 3/7/07 @ 4 PM University Hall Atrium for photos of Susan Herbst shaking hands with students or a group shot of Susan with some students., 2007 March 7; 26.1 MB 60 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 3/15/07 @ 4 - 5 P.M. at the Downtown Campus in Milne 215 for photo of the Campus Book Project Reading Discussion Group, 2007 March 14; 15.7 MB 33 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 3/16/07 @ 12:15 PM Campus Center (exact location tbd) for photos of students watching the UAlbany Basketball v Vermont., 2007 March 16; 62.8 MB 127 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 3/28/07 @ 9 AM corner of Washington & Quail for Safe Corridor Press Event (series of speakers), 2007 March 29; 110.2 MB 99 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 4/20/07 @ 11 a.m. University Hall Atrium for Biodiversity Event announcement., 2007 April 20; 28.2 MB 39 Digital Files
      - PSC: Photo session - picture of new Psych. Services Center Building for inclusion in 2 brochures (job #'s 20004982 and 4983), 2007 April 23; 82.2 MB 124 Digital Files
      - President's Office: 4/17/07 @ 5 PM Small Fountain for Candle Light Vigil., 2007 April 23; 18.2 MB 54 Digital Files
      - Provost: 4/23/07 @ 3 - 5 PM Campus Center Ballroom for Award of Excellence ceremony, 2007 April 23; 21.5 MB 43 Digital Files
      - Alumni Association: Photo Session; various locations for Alumni Weekend_07; email to follow with specific locations and times, 2007 April 24; 383.2 MB 473 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 4/30/07 @ 2:30 PM meet at Standish Room and then photograph as they tour School of Education and Uptown Campus for News in Photos., 2007 April 26; 27.2 MB 55 Digital Files
      - Center for Women in Government: 4/25/07, Campus Center Ballroom for Language Access Conference during the following times: 9 - 10:30 a.m. for Welcome and Keynote 12:30 - 1:30 p.m. for lunch presentation 4:15 - 5:15 p.m for final session, concluding remarks, and full group photo, 2007 April 26; 219.7 MB 150 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/17/07 @ 11:30 AM 299 Washington Ave Albany, NY Psychological Services Center Re-Opening Celebration, 2007 April 30; 39.1 MB 41 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/16/07 @ 3 PN CC Small Fountain Holocaust Rememberance w/ Susan Herbst reading names of survivors, 2007 April 30; 36.2 MB 33 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 4/17/07 @ 11:30 AM 299 Washington Ave Albany, NY Psychological Services Center Re-Opening Celebration, 2007 April 30; 39.1 MB 41 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 5/9/07 @ 5 PM (will confirm) University Hall Atrium for Stone Exhibit event., 2007 May 2; 40.0 MB 70 Digital Files
      - Libraries: 5/3/07 @ 2 - 4 pm Standish Room, Science Library for Bread and Roses event, 2007 May 3; 189.2 MB 101 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 5/14/07 @ 11:45 AM - 1 PM, Marriott Hotel for Citizen Bank check presentation to University., 2007 May 14; 15.8 MB 31 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 6/18 @ 9:15 AM Campus Center, 2nd Floor for Alcohol Summit News Conference with Mayor, Chancellor and Officer in Charge Susan Herbst., 2007 June 18; 86.8 MB 122 Digital Files
      - NEPHLI: 7/17/07 @ 12 Noon Rensselaerville Institute, 2007 July 17; 54.1 MB 138 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing:; Alumni Awareness luncheon, campus ctr ballroom on Oct. 12th noon - 2 p.m., 2007 August 14; 376.4 MB 186 Digital Files
      - Informatics: MSIS faculty and master students 8/28/07 from 12 - 1:30 p.m. in MILNE 200, just general shots of interaction, 2007 August 31; 24.1 MB 63 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: photos in front of small fountain for Kermit Hall's remeberence ceremony, 2007 September 7; 98.5 MB 79 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: photos of Chinese ambassador with his group as well as with Susan Herbst on 9/5/07. Event starts at 3 p.m. in UHALL atrium, please arrive earlier since you have a shoot at athletics at 3:45 p.m., 2007 September 13; 23.8 MB 48 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: Mara-Tisch field naming on 8/17/07 @ 4 p.m., 2007 September 19; 113.2 MB 139 Digital Files
      - Advancement Events: 10/13/07 from 9:30 - 11:00 a.m. in the Standish Room, Champagne Jazz Brunch., 2007 September 26; 56.4 MB 103 Digital Files
      - Advancement Events: 11/8/07 from 6 - 9 p.m.@ the Hall of Springs in Saratoga for the Citizen Laureate Awards., 2007 September 26; 83.0 MB 186 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 9/17/07 @ 1 p.m. in the Assembly Hall to take shot of Steve Kroft talking w/students, then on to the Medallion ceremony in the Fireside lounge @ 2:30 to get shots of him receiving medallion., 2007 September 28; 58.0 MB 111 Digital Files
      - 9/20/07 @ 9 a.m. Apt. 215 Heritage Rd. Apts., go to intersection of route 20 and route 155, turn south on to route 155 and take left to heritage village, go to end of heritage rd. 3 story apt. bldg, apt. 215. call 452-5429 if you need assistance. * Please bring a back drop! * Is looking for a shot of the 11 books he wrote all in one photo., 2007 October 1; 35.0 MB 13 Digital Files
      - University Events: 12/8/07 from 6 - 9 p.m. at the SEFCU Arena, Gala honoring Mayor Jennings, 2007 October 25; 252.3 MB 348 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 10/19/07 at 1 p.m. to take photos fof purple path ground breaking ceremony. Location is SEFCU Arena parking lot near Western Ave side., 2007 October 25; 36.8 MB 61 Digital Files
      - Student Success: 10/15/07 at 2:30 p.m for plaque dedication in memory of Kermit Hall. Location is in front of the Science Library bldg (west garden of the podium)., 2007 October 25; 37.6 MB 63 Digital Files
      - University Events: 12/8/07 from 6 - 9 p.m. at the SEFCU Arena, Gala honoring Mayor Jennings, 2007 October 25; 252.3 MB 348 Digital Files
      - University Events: 10/23/07 at 11:30 a.m. at the Cancer Center on the East Campus. Massry Conference Center Dedication and Luncheon. Please get shots of the Massrys w/various people, Sen. Bruno, George Hearst, George Philip and Susan Herbst. Should conclude at 2 pm., 2007 October 25; 38.1 MB 101 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 10/12/07 at 10:00 a.m. Farmer's market on the podium in front of Campus Center. Take shots for news in photos, looking for color, students buying things and activity., 2007 October 26; 25.6 MB 47 Digital Files
      - Small Business Development Center: Photo Session: 10/30/07 @ 11 AM Materials Recovery Company, 1 Monroe St., Troy, NY for photos to include in SBDC Annual Report, 2007 October 30; 27.6 MB 37 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 10/17/07 at 3:30 at Empire Commons to take shot of Matt Ryan and also Matt with Andrei Lapenas. Shot of Matt for home page. Go Green initiative for conserving electrical energy., 2007 October 31; 35.5 MB 80 Digital Files
      - University Events: 10/31/07 from 3 - 5 p.m. for Celebrating Teaching in the D'ambra Auditorium in the life sciences bldg. to take general shots of event., 2007 November 8; 42.8 MB 80 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 10/26/07 from 2:30 - 4 p.m. to take shots of farewell event for Susan Herbst., 2007 November 9; 42.2 MB 36 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 11/7/07 at 11 a.m. at the small fountain to take shots of press conference celebrating John Lowery for his National Award from American Cancer Society., 2007 November 16; 26.9 MB 39 Digital Files
      - Center for Women in Tech & Gov't.: 11/9/07 from 2:45 - 3:45 at the Italian American Community Center to take shots of Women's cargiving forum. Get general shots and shots of panel speakers., 2007 November 21; 29.6 MB 61 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 11/7/07 @ 10 AM CC Lobby RSVP Craft Fair, 2007 November 21; 19.7 MB 23 Digital Files
      - English: 11/9/07 from 9 - 10:30 at the Standish room to take "dynamic" shots of Ecologies of War conference for english web site., 2007 November 21; 9.3 MB 19 Digital Files
      - Development: 11/29/07 @ 12 - 1:30 p.m., Standish Room, Science Library for Valedictorian luncheon. Type of shots needed: general shots of event & students with their professors and a group shot of all the honorees., 2007 November 21; 23.1 MB 50 Digital Files
      - University Events: 11/27/07 from 8 - 9 a.m. in the SEFCU Hall of Fame room to take shots of speakers and crowd for CEO breakfast featuring Lee McElroy., 2007 November 21; 48.3 MB 78 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 11/9/07 @ 11 AM CC Ballroom Welcome for George Philip, 2007 November 23; 8.9 MB 14 Digital Files
      - Provost: photo sesssion: 11/13/07 @ 5 PM UAB 423 Anniversary Celebration of Emeritus Center, 2007 November 28; 12.1 MB 29 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 12/12/07 @ 1:30 at Harriman Campus, Building 3 for news conference., 2007 December 12; 64.9 MB 78 Digital Files
      - Center for Women in Government & Civil: 1/11/08 @ 10:45 AM - 12 Noon, Draper 105 for head shots and a group photo of our Fellows on Women and Public Policy. (Location for group photo could be front of Draper Hall, or perhaps the Dewey Library), 2008 January 12; 78.8 MB 183 Digital Files
      - Media Relations: 1/25/08 @ 1:30 PM Patroon Lounge, for photo of George Philip at Friends exhibit lunch to be used in News in Photo and possible release. Type of shot: George interacting with people or pointing at exhibit with exhibit as backdrop., 2008 January 17; 48.0 MB 62 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 2/8/08 @ 3 PM in LC1 for Darwin Day event., 2008 February 8; 5.4 MB 12 Digital Files
      - Media Relations: 2/7/08 @ 12 Noon, CC Ballroom for Martin Luther King Jr. Event. Speaker: Myrlie Evers-Willilams. Types of shots: speaker at the podium, possibly interacting with UAlbany officials and students., 2008 February 8; 88.4 MB 93 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 2/5/08 @ 8 am HOF room SEFCU Arena Breakfast of Champions, 2008 February 19; 114.3 MB 63 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 2/13/08 @ 11:30 AM Sefcu Arena Job fair / exposition, 2008 February 27; 26.1 MB 53 Digital Files
      - President's Office: 2/27/08 @ 1 PM in UNH 302 (George's Office) for photo of Brandy Barnard - new UPD Officer being sworn in., 2008 February 27; 19.4 MB 27 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: Photo Session: 3/3/08, 11:00 AM for Giants sign unveiling:, 2008 March 3; 28.2 MB 50 Digital Files
      - Economics Dept: Photo session: 3/7/08 @ 2:30 - 4:00 @ Economics Dept for Nobel Laureate Robert Engle., 2008 March 7; 25.1 MB 52 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 2/28/08 @ 12:00 PM in the Campus Center for Relay for Life photo., 2008 March 12; 25.1 MB 26 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: 3/3/08 @ 3:30 PM in the Blue Room at the Capital for photo of state authors., 2008 March 12; 155.9 MB 187 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 2/28/08 @ 10:30 am UNH Atrium Presidential Scholar Educational Failr, 2008 March 13; 136.4 MB 96 Digital Files
      - University Events: Photo session: 3/18/08 from 4:30 to 6:30 PM @the Empire State Plaza for UAlbany Advocacy Day., 2008 March 18; 278.7 MB 233 Digital Files
      - University Events: Photo session: 3/18/08 from 4:30 to 6:30 PM @the Empire State Plaza for UAlbany Advocacy Day., 2008 March 18; 278.7 MB 233 Digital Files
      - President's Office: Photo session: 3/27/08 Congressman McNulty visit at the M.E. Grenander Dept of Special Collections and Archives (Science Library) at 9:30 am., 2008 March 27; 39.7 MB 91 Digital Files
      - Marketing Services: Photo session: 4/1/08 at 10 AM for defibrillator training for faculty/staff at the Campus Center Assembly Hall., 2008 April 1; 85.0 MB 50 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/5/08 @ 3:00 p.m. Relay for Life at the SEFCU Arena, 2008 April 5; 693.0 MB 368 Digital Files
      - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/7/08 The public effects of global climate change lecture from 3-4 p.m. at the East Campus. Dr. Julie Gerberding, 2008 April 7; 114.4 MB 64 Digital Files